Office of the President Mary Maples Dunn Files, 1985-1995
Smith College Archives
- SERIES X. ENGAGEMENTS, (5 document boxes / 2.1 linear feet)
  - Daily Schedules
    - -Aug-Dec 1993 Aug-Dec 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Jan-May 1994 Jan-May 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -Jun-Dec 1994 Jun-Dec 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Jan-Jun 1995 Jan-Jun 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Refusals
    - -Jan-May 1986 Jan-May 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -Jun-Dec 1986 Jun-Dec 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -1990 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -1994 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Travel Schedules
    - -1985-1986 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -1987-1993 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- SERIES XI. EVENTS, (7 document boxes / 2.9 linear feet)
  Along with the Speeches and Engagements series, the records in this series document the activities and responsibilities of the President of Smith College. The events in this series (as opposed to the Engagements series) include significant campus traditional gatherings and celebrations as well as one-time happenings. Routine events include assemblies, commencement, Rally Day, and the awarding of Smith College Medals and honorary degrees. Other events include Dunn's inauguration, concerts, conferences, symposia, lectures, as well as various events at the President's House.
  - Commencement (Box 1)
    - - 1986
      - -General 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - -Speaker 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - - 1987
      - -General 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - -Speaker 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - - 1988
      - -General (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - -Shavuoth Conflict 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - -Speaker 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - - 1989
      - -General 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - -Speaker 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -1990 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - - 1991
      - -General 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - -Shavuoth 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - -Speaker 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - - 1992
      - -General 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - -Speaker 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -1993 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - -1994 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conferences
    - -About Women: Teaching and Research at Smith 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - -China Today 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - -Civil Rights/Institutional Diversity
      - -General 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - -Handouts 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - -Encuentro de Latinas 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - -Experiences of Black Students 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Faces of Tradition: Germany In Europe 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Kathleen Ridder Conference 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Model United Nations 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Women and Leadership, proposed 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dunn Celebration Day 1995 (Box 2)
    - -Publicity (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Gifts 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Invitations and Lists 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Meeting Minutes 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Memos 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -Programs and Schedules 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -Transportation and Accommodations 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Family Weekend 1986-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration
    - -Program 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -Inaugural Address 1985 (Box 2)
      - -Final Copy 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - -Background Info 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - -Drafts 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - -Publicity 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -Speakers and Distinguished Guests 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - -Order of Exercises 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - -Event Schedules 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - -Accompanying Events 1985 (Box 2)
      - -Chapel Service 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - -Debate 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - -Museum Exhibit and Concert 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - -Music 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - -"Presidential Search" Game 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - -Symposium 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -Menus 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Recipe Books 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -"Transplantable Inauguration Garden Party" 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Welcome Packet 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Invitations 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -Guest Lists
        - -General 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - -Academic Delegates 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - -Alumnae 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - -MMD Personal 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - -Replies 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - -Congratulations 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Thank-You Notes
      - -Incoming 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -Outgoing 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Planning
      - -General 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Arrangements for Guests 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -Budget and Expenses 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - -Inaugural Committee Meetings 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - -Seating, Processional 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - -Rain Contingency 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Interterm 1985-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Last Chapel 1986 (Box 4)
    - -1986 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - -1987 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - -1988 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - -1989 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - -1990-1993 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lecturers and Visiting Scholars
    - -General 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - -Foreign Visitors Welcoming Committee 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - -Kyung-Nan Choo 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Tropp, Vladimir 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mountain Day 1988-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Opening Convocation
    - -1985-1988 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -1989 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -1990-1991 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -1992 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Otelia Cromwell Day
    - -1989 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -Feb 1991 Feb 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Oct 1991 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -1992 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -1993 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - President's House Events
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - -General 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - -General 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -Monthly Schedules
      - -1985-1987 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - -1988-1989 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - -1990-1991 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - -1992-1993 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - -1994-1995 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -Head Residents Dinners 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -Presidential Intern Dinners 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -Senior Dinners 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -Spectrum Dinners 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rally Day
    - -1986 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - -1987 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - -1988 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -1989 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - -1990 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - - 1991
      - -General 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - -Medalists 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - - 1992
      - -General 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - -Medallists 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -1993 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -1995 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Summer Programs 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Symposia
    - -Century of Struggle/Flexner Celebration 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -Metanoetics 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -Teaching for Tomorrow 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - -WAVES (proposed) 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball Centennial 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- SERIES XII. FACULTY & STAFF, (2 document boxes / 0.8 linear feet)
  The records in this series document the relationship of the President's Office with faculty and staff. There is information on a number of general faculty and staff issues, such as salaries and retirement, as well as information about specific individuals. Material relating to emeritus faculty and staff (including former Smith presidents and their families) can be found in this series as well.
  Additional material for specific faculty or staff members may be found in the Academic Departments, Administrative Offices, or Committees and Boards series. The Committees and Boards series also includes records for a number of faculty and staff-related committees. The records of the Women and Social Change Project, a faculty-research endeavor, is also included in this series.
  - General 1985-1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Staff 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clerical/Administrative Coffee Hour 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Forums 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Emeritus Presidents and Their Families
    - -Conway 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Davis 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Mendenhall 1985, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Equal Opportunity Policy and Grievance Procedures
    - -1988-Mar 1989 1988-Mar 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Apr-Aug 1989 Apr-Aug 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Club 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Dinners
    - -Jan-Mar 1992 Jan-Mar 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Apr 1992-1994 Apr 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Entertainment Funds 1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Salaries 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Spouse Tuition Policy 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences Luncheons 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Individuals
    - -A-C 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Berenson, Senda (Box 2)
        See Series XVI. Students-Athletics-Basketball
    - -D-F 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Dalby, Sidonia 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Freccero, Yvonne 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -G-L 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -Horowitz, Helen and Daniel 1994-1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Hoyt, Nelly 1989-1990, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -M-R 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -S-Z 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - -Schalk, Marshall 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - -Smith, Eleanor 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - -Unsworth, Richard 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - -Von Klemperer, Elizabeth and Klemens 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Miscellaneous 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Labor Unions 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Minority Faculty
    - -General 1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -Mendenhall Fellows 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Neilson Professors
    - -General 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -Charles Hamilton 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Roy S. Bryce-Laporte 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -Trinh Minh-La 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - OBND (Out But Not Down) 1985, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Policies
    - -General 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -TIAA/CREF 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Smith Administrative Management Seminar (Box 3)
    - -1988, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Staff Connection 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Voluntary Separation Packages (Box 3)
    See Series V. Admin. Offices-Development-Fdns-Mellon Fdn (1992 and 1993).
    Series IX. Committees & Boards-Resource Allocation, Advisory Committee. Series IX. Committees & Boards-Transition, Advisory Committee on. Series IX. Committees & Boards-Strategic Planning Committees
  - Women Faculty (Box 3)
    See Series VI. Alumnae-Individuals-Rosenfeld, Erika, for a 1986 letter to the SAQ about ratio of men to women on the faculty.
  - Women and Social Change Project 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Ford Foundation
  - Wye Faculty Seminars 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- SERIES XIII. GRADUATE WORK, (2 document boxes / 0.8 linear feet)
  The Graduate Work series includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, and reports regarding the evolution and operation of several graduate studies programs at the college. There are records documenting general aspects of graduate education, as well as specific programs of study, such as the the Smith-Northampton Summer School, the Smith Management Program, and the School of Social Work.
  Useful information may also be found in the Committees and Boards series on the Committee on Graduate Study.
  - Education and Child Study (Box 1)
    - -SAGE [Smith Association of Graduate Education Students] 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -Smith/Northampton Summer School 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - School for Social Work
    - -Annual Reports 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -General 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -General Jan-Mar 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -General Apr-Dec 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -General 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -General 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -General 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -70th Anniversary 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -75th Anniversary 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - -Commencement 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -Day-Garrett Award 1991-1993, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - -Doctoral Program Review 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Honorary Letters to Field Faculty 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Honorary Letters to Field Faculty 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Honorary Letters to Field Faculty 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -Salem State College 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Self Study, Vol. 1 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Strategic Plan 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Ten Year Trends Study 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Smith Management Program
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Corporations-Citicorp
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -General 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -General 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Staff Nominations 1986-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- SERIES XIV. INTERCOLLEGIATE ASSOCIATIONS, (7 document boxes / 2.9 linear feet)
  There are four intercollegiate associations included in this series: Five Colleges, Inc., Seven Sisters, Society Organized Against Racism, and Women's College Coalition.
  Five Colleges: The Five Colleges material includes correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings tracing the evolution of cooperative relations between Smith College, Mount Holyoke College, Hampshire College, Amherst College, and the University of Massachusetts at Amherst.
  Seven Sisters: The records of the Seven Sisters (also known as the Seven Colleges) include correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings documenting relations between seven of the most important historically women-only colleges in the Eastern United States: Barnard, Bryn Mawr, Mount Holyoke, Radcliffe, Smith, Vassar, and Wellesley.
  Society Organized Against Racism (SOAR): The SOAR records include correspondence and reports documenting the founding and early activity of the organization. SOAR, founded in 1982, is a consortium of New England colleges and universities working to improve the racial climate in academic institutions.
  Women's College Coalition: The Women's College Coalition was founded in 1972 under the auspices of the Association of American Colleges. It includes more than seventy two- and four-year colleges. The material in this collection includes correspondence, reports and announcements of the organization's events and projects.
  - Five Colleges
    - -General 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - -Coordinator 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - -Directors Meetings 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - -Directors Meetings 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - -Directors Meetings 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Directors Meetings 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Academic Departments & Programs
      - -American Studies (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Arabic Studies [proposed] 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - -Canadian Studies 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -Constitutional Studies (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Dance Program 1985- (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -East Asian Studies 1986- (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - -European Institute [proposed] 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - -Film Studies (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - -Foreign Languages & Culture 1988- (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - -Gerontology 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - -History 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - -Irish Studies (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - -Latin American Studies 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - -Peace and World Security Studies 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - -Poetry 1988- (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - -Political Science 1989- (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - -Sciences
        - -General 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - -Astronomy 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - -Coastal and Marine Sciences 1985- (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - -Theatre (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -Women's Studies 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -American Indian Student Association 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -Articles of Incorporation Amendments 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - -Budget 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - -Budget 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Five Colleges
    - -Budget 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Budget 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Calendar Coordination 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Citizens for Limited Taxation Proposal (Question 3) 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Grants and Proposals
      - -General 1985-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -NEH Challenge Grant 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -"Growing Without Growing" Report 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -Historic Deerfield Cooperation 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Interchange 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -Learning In Retirement Program 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -Libraries
      - -General 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - -General 1987- (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - -Boss Report 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - -OCLC Agreement 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - -OCLC Agreement Revision 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Living Care Center 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -Massachusetts Review 1985- (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Minority Fellows Program 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -Minority Student Recruitment 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Museum Collaboration 1993, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -Public School Partnership 1985-1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -Radio - WFCR 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Telecommunications 1985-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -Transportation System 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Seven Sisters 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Seven Sisters 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Seven Sisters 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Society Organized Against Racism 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Society Organized Against Racism 1988-1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Women's College Coalition 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women's College Coalition 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Women's College Coalition 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Women's College Coalition 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Women's College Coalition Jan-Jun 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Women's College Coalition Jul-Dec 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Women's College Coalition 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Women's College Coalition 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Women's College Coalition 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Women's College Coalition 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- SERIES XV. NON-SMITH ORGANIZATIONS, (9 document boxes / 3.8 linear feet)
  The files in this series are organized alphabetically by organization name, with a number of miscellaneous organizations also filed alphabetically, in the last few boxes.
  The material in this series documents the variety of national, regional and local organizations which had an impact on, and a relationship with, Smith College. Included are reports, newspaper clippings and correspondence with a number of academic, civic, corporate and nonprofit organizations. Organizations of particular interest are the Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts (AICUM), the Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), and state and federal government bodies.
  - Advisory Council on Women / Lenox Associates 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Association of Presidents of Independent Colleges and Univs. 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Collegiate Consortium for East-West Cultural and Academic Exchange Apr 1987-May 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Collegiate Consortium for East-West Cultural and Academic Exchange Jun 1988-Aug 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education
    - -General 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -General 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Board of Directors 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Women in Higher Education 1985-Aug 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Women in Higher Education Sep 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Societies 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Association of American Colleges 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Colleges 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Association of American Colleges 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges 1986-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in MA [AICUM] 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in MA 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in MA 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in MA 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Catalyst 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - College Board 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Conference Board 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Consortium for the Education of Non-Traditional Students (Box 2)
    See Series III. Academic Programs-Ada Comstock Scholars
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education [COFHE] 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Jan-Apr 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education May-Jul 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Aug-Dec 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cooley's - Marco Polo Inc (Box 4)
    See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Wedgewood Commemorative China
  - Cooperative Institutional Research Program [CIRP] 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Council of Independent Colleges 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Council of Independent Colleges 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Council of Independent Colleges 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Freeform Enterprises 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Humanities Research Institute 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Leadership Project 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - International Association of Students in Economics and Commerce [AIESEC] [sic] 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Korn/Ferry International 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Learned Colleagues (Box 5)
    - -General 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -General 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -General 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -Smith Meeting June 24-26, 1992 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Association of Non-Profit Schools and Colleges 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Board of Regents of Higher Education 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)